Why do you look so content?
ทำไมคุณดูพอใจจัง
Because you've tried your best, so you don't regret it?
เพราะพยายามเต็มที่แล้วไม่เสียใจเหรอ?
Why did you give up so easily?
ทำไมคุณยอมแพ้ง่ายจัง
You should be greedier.
คุณควรจะโลภมากขึ้น
You should have begged for your life.
คุณควรได้ร้องขอชีวิตของคุณ
Who am I, who struggle to survive,
ฉันเป็นใคร ที่ต่อสู้ดิ้นรนเพื่อเอาชีวิตรอด
who do everything to live?
ใครทำทุกอย่างเพื่อมีชีวิตอยู่?
Araba!
รถยนต์!
I was attacked by various creatures after reincarnation,
ฉันถูกโจมตีโดยสิ่งมีชีวิตต่าง ๆ หลังจากการกลับชาติมาเกิด
as if I was in a field battle.
ราวกับว่าฉันอยู่ในสนามรบ
I can finally go to the outside-world.
ในที่สุดฉันก็สามารถไปสู่โลกภายนอกได้
Hooray!
ไชโย!
It's outside! I'm free!
มันอยู่ข้างนอก! ฉันว่าง!
What is this?
นี่คืออะไร?
I thought I'm free. But I'm trapped inside again.
ฉันคิดว่าฉันว่าง แต่ฉันกลับติดอยู่ข้างใน
It hurts.
มันเจ็บ.
I'm so angry...
ฉันโกรธมาก...
It isn't a good idea to kill all of them now. I should just control my power.
ไม่ควรฆ่าพวกเขาทั้งหมดตอนนี้ ฉันควรจะควบคุมพลังของฉัน
You asked for it!
คุณขอมัน!
♫The alarm goes off. My name is Little Spider♫
♫นาฬิกาปลุกดับลง ฉันชื่อแมงมุมน้อย♫
EPISODE 13: YAY, THE OUTSIDE. I'M FREE? ♫The awakening survival skill♫
ตอนที่ 13: เย้ ข้างนอก ฉันว่าง? ♫ทักษะการเอาชีวิตรอดที่ตื่นขึ้น♫
♫No obstacles can stop me♫
ตอนที่ 13: เย้ ข้างนอก ฉันว่าง? ♫ไม่มีอุปสรรคใดหยุดฉันได้♫
♫Go! Dark clouds♫
♫ไป! เมฆมืด♫
♫Sometimes I pretend it's fate♫
♫บางครั้งฉันก็แสร้งทำเป็นว่าโชคชะตา♫
♫The 3-D perspective street that appears in the intersection of good and evil♫
♫ถนนมุมมอง 3 มิติ ที่ปรากฏอยู่ในทางแยกของความดีและความชั่ว♫
♫The labyrinth of nightmares is nothing to me♫
♫เขาวงกตแห่งฝันร้ายไม่มีความหมายสำหรับฉัน♫
♫Common sense isn't useful here♫
♫สามัญสำนึกไม่มีประโยชน์ที่นี่♫
♫Charging forward like a man is naive♫
♫ พุ่งไปข้างหน้าเหมือนผู้ชายไร้เดียงสา ♫
♫Because life isn't as easy as you think♫
♫เพราะชีวิตไม่ได้ง่ายอย่างที่คิด♫
♫It drives me forward♫
♫มันขับเคลื่อนฉันไปข้างหน้า♫
♫These hands created a brave me♫
♫มือเหล่านี้สร้างฉันให้กล้าหาญ♫
♫Excuse me, I'm the strongest!♫
♫ขอโทษนะ ฉันแข็งแกร่งที่สุด!♫
♫The violent and greedy spider is riding the wind♫
♫แมงมุมที่ดุร้ายและโลภกำลังขี่สายลม♫
♫The unpredictable waves♫
♫คลื่นที่คาดเดาไม่ได้♫
♫It's not the end yet♫
♫ ยังไม่จบ ♫
♫Use the fastest speed to pass through darkness♫
♫ใช้ความเร็วที่เร็วที่สุดเพื่อผ่านความมืด♫
♫Because we only live once♫
♫เพราะเรามีชีวิตอยู่เพียงครั้งเดียว♫
♫As long as we keep running forward♫
♫ตราบใดที่เรายังคงวิ่งไปข้างหน้า♫
♫Loosen the knot in your heart♫
♫ คลายปมในใจเธอ ♫
♫So you can jump right onto the next exciting stage♫
♫เพื่อให้คุณสามารถกระโดดไปยังเวทีที่น่าตื่นเต้นถัดไป♫
Bathing under the sun.
อาบน้ำใต้แสงแดด.
Birdie, how are you?
เบอร์ดี้ สบายดีไหม
Butterflies.
ผีเสื้อ.
I'm not a hungry spider. I will not eat you.
ฉันไม่ใช่แมงมุมหิว ฉันจะไม่กินคุณ
I didn't expect the world to be so colourful.
ฉันไม่ได้คาดหวังว่าโลกจะมีสีสันมากขนาดนี้
Seriously? Humans are really noisy.
อย่างจริงจัง? มนุษย์มีเสียงดังจริงๆ
What's going on?
เกิดอะไรขึ้น?
Okay, forget them.
โอเค ลืมพวกเขาไปเลย
Let's see where I can find good food.
มาดูกันว่าจะหาของอร่อยได้ที่ไหนบ้าง
It's a town! Perhaps there are desserts.
มันเป็นเมือง! บางทีก็มีขนม
Hold on.
เดี๋ยวก่อน
Hi, I'm an adorable little spider. Please give me something sweet to eat.
สวัสดี ฉันเป็นแมงมุมตัวน้อยที่น่ารัก ขอของหวานกินหน่อย
A monster!
ปีศาจ!
Kill her!
ฆ่าเธอ!
I'm sure that's what will happen.
ฉันแน่ใจว่านั่นคือสิ่งที่จะเกิดขึ้น
Forget it, then.
ลืมมันไปเถอะ
I wonder if I can turn to human form after evolution.
ฉันสงสัยว่าฉันสามารถแปลงร่างเป็นมนุษย์หลังจากวิวัฒนาการได้หรือไม่
Spider Lady.
นางแมงมุม.
This is...
นี่คือ...
A human's upper body.
ร่างกายส่วนบนของมนุษย์
If I can evolve to this state, the chance of being hunted will decrease.
ถ้าฉันสามารถพัฒนาไปสู่สถานะนี้ได้ โอกาสในการถูกล่าจะลดลง
That's right.
ถูกตัอง.
Compared to an innocent spider, a human face
เปรียบได้กับแมงมุมบริสุทธิ์หน้าคน human
can make people be less alert.
สามารถทำให้คนตื่นตัวน้อยลง
Perhaps. Plausible. For sure. Maybe.
บางที. เป็นไปได้ อย่างแน่นอน อาจจะ.
I want to work towards Spider Lady.
ฉันต้องการทำงานกับ Spider Lady
I'm a hungry spider.
ฉันเป็นแมงมุมหิว
Forget it.
ลืมมันไปเถอะ
Hey.
เฮ้.
This is not a labyrinth without any good food.
นี่ไม่ใช่เขาวงกตที่ไม่มีอาหารดีๆ
There should be some delicious food.
น่าจะมีของอร่อย
Let's see.
มาดูกัน.
I don't care if it's some mushrooms, bamboo shoots or chocolate.
ฉันไม่สนหรอกว่าจะเป็นเห็ด หน่อไม้ หรือช็อคโกแลต
What's going on?
เกิดอะไรขึ้น?
Mother?
แม่?
What? You want me to be back?
อะไร? คุณต้องการให้ฉันกลับมาไหม
Family Domination. What is this?
การปกครองครอบครัว นี่คืออะไร?
Do they mean it literally?
พวกเขาหมายถึงมันอย่างแท้จริง?
Turns out mother has the ability to control her children.
ปรากฎว่าแม่มีความสามารถในการควบคุมลูกของเธอ
That means I have to go back to the labyrinth.
นั่นหมายความว่าฉันต้องกลับไปที่เขาวงกต
Perhaps not.
อาจจะไม่.
"INVALID GAIDO" I see. Thanks to this.
"ไกโดไม่ถูกต้อง" ฉันเห็น ขอบคุณสิ่งนี้
I will not obey to orders.
ฉันจะไม่เชื่อฟังคำสั่ง
I insist on rejecting such orders.
ฉันยืนกรานที่จะปฏิเสธคำสั่งดังกล่าว
No. I'm a Japanese person who knows how to say no.
ไม่ ฉันเป็นคนญี่ปุ่นที่รู้วิธีปฏิเสธ
But I'm neither Japanese nor a person now.
แต่ตอนนี้ฉันไม่ใช่คนญี่ปุ่นและไม่ใช่คน
I feel that mother is very angry.
ฉันรู้สึกว่าแม่โกรธมาก
You shall be mad underground forever.
คุณจะบ้าอยู่ใต้ดินตลอดไป
After all, you will not be able to be out with your big body.
ท้ายที่สุดคุณจะไม่สามารถออกไปเที่ยวกับร่างใหญ่ของคุณได้
Goodbye, mother.
ลาก่อนแม่
I, who defeated Araba, am not afraid of my weak mother.
ฉันที่เอาชนะอาราบา ไม่กลัวแม่ที่อ่อนแอของฉัน
Let's go look for some good food.
ไปหาของอร่อยกินกัน
I'm coming in.
ฉันกำลังเข้ามา
It's time to go.
ถึงเวลาที่จะไป
Okay, I get it.
โอเค ฉันเข้าใจ
Hi.
สวัสดี
Brother Hyrince.
พี่ไฮรินซ์.
How are you, Shun?
เป็นไงบ้างชุน?
Odd. Isn't she...
คี่ เธอไม่ใช่เหรอ...
She's Anna, my servant. She has been serving me since I was small.
เธอคือแอนนา คนใช้ของฉัน เธอรับใช้ฉันตั้งแต่ฉันยังเล็ก
I'm Anna. Long time no see, Mr. Hyrince.
ฉันแอนนา ไม่เจอกันนานเลยนะคุณไฮรินซ์
I've seen you many times when I visited the castle with Julius. Nice to see you.
ฉันเคยเห็นคุณหลายครั้งเมื่อฉันไปที่ปราสาทกับจูเลียส ดีใจที่ได้พบคุณ.
Shun, do you want to have dinner with me tonight?
ชุน คืนนี้คุณอยากทานอาหารเย็นกับฉันไหม
Sorry. I have a meeting with the clan leader of the elves.
ขอโทษ ฉันมีนัดกับหัวหน้าเผ่าเอลฟ์
I see. What a shame. Let's do it next time then.
ฉันเห็น. สิ่งที่น่าละอาย คราวหน้าค่อยว่ากันอีกที
Okay.
ตกลง.
I'm the clan leader of the elves, Potimas.
ข้าคือหัวหน้าเผ่าเอลฟ์ โปติมัส
I'm Filimøs. Nice to meet you.
ฉันชื่อFilimøs ยินดีที่ได้รู้จัก.
Your Highness Potimas, these are my sons.
ฝ่าบาท Potimas นี่คือลูกชายของฉัน
I'm Cylis. Nice to meet you.
ฉันชื่อไซลิส ยินดีที่ได้รู้จัก.
I'm Leston. Regarding the great deeds of Potimas, Oka...
ฉันเลสตัน เกี่ยวกับความยิ่งใหญ่ของ Potimas, Oka...
Filimøs has told us about it.
Filimøs ได้บอกเราเกี่ยวกับเรื่องนี้
I'm Schlain. Nice to meet you.
ฉันชเลน ยินดีที่ได้รู้จัก.
I believe the fellow elves know that the humans and demons are having war.
ฉันเชื่อว่าเพื่อนเอลฟ์รู้ว่ามนุษย์และปีศาจกำลังทำสงคราม
In order to avoid wars, I wanted to reconcile with Demon Clan. We negotiated,
เพื่อหลีกเลี่ยงสงคราม ฉันต้องการคืนดีกับ Demon Clan เราเจรจา
but I wasn't capable enough and caused conflicts.
แต่ฉันไม่มีความสามารถเพียงพอและก่อให้เกิดความขัดแย้ง
If I could do better, Julius wouldn't...
ถ้าฉันทำได้ดีกว่านี้ จูเลียสจะไม่...
You've tried your best to convince them.
คุณได้พยายามอย่างดีที่สุดเพื่อโน้มน้าวพวกเขา
This is an unavoidable war.
นี่คือสงครามที่หลีกเลี่ยงไม่ได้
Things that have happened can't be turned back.
สิ่งที่เกิดขึ้นไม่สามารถย้อนกลับได้
What happened to Julius is a shame, but instead of missing him,
สิ่งที่เกิดขึ้นกับจูเลียสเป็นความอัปยศ แต่แทนที่จะคิดถึงเขา
we should figure out a strategy to deal with them.
เราควรหากลยุทธ์ที่จะจัดการกับพวกเขา
Fortunately, we have a new Warrior.
โชคดีที่เรามีนักรบใหม่
I think we should have Schlain in battle as soon as possible to stop them.
ฉันคิดว่าเราควรให้ Schlain ในการต่อสู้โดยเร็วที่สุดเพื่อหยุดพวกเขา
Brother, Schlain is just a student. How can you have in a battle?
บราเดอร์ Schlain เป็นแค่นักเรียน คุณจะมีการต่อสู้ได้อย่างไร?
Julius was even younger than him when he was battling as Warrior.
จูเลียสอายุน้อยกว่าเขาเมื่อเขาต่อสู้ในฐานะนักรบ
I...
ผม...
No. The battle situation is still unclear.
ไม่ สถานการณ์การต่อสู้ยังไม่ชัดเจน
It's not the best idea to rush to send the Warrior to the field.
ไม่ใช่ความคิดที่ดีที่สุดที่จะรีบส่งนักรบไปที่สนาม
But father...
แต่พ่อ...
King Analeit is right.
พระเจ้าอนาเลอิตพูดถูก
Why do you say so, Mr. Potimas?
ทำไมคุณถึงพูดอย่างนั้น คุณโพธิมาศ?
The current Devil...
ปีศาจในปัจจุบัน...
She has stronger power than any previous Devil.
เธอมีพลังที่แข็งแกร่งกว่าปีศาจตัวก่อนๆ
I suffered because of her as well.
ฉันก็ทุกข์เพราะเธอเหมือนกัน
Since she became Devil, the successful communication with Demon Clan has been stopped.
ตั้งแต่เธอกลายเป็นปีศาจ การสื่อสารที่ประสบความสำเร็จกับ Demon Clan ก็หยุดลง
Besides, she has subordinates that are hard to deal with.
นอกจากนี้ เธอมีลูกน้องที่รับมือยาก
Therefore, it's not wise to do anything before having intelligence.
ดังนั้นจึงไม่ควรทำอะไรก่อนที่จะมีสติปัญญา
Is there anything?
มีอะไรหรือเปล่า?
After you became Warrior, you have to deal with The Religion of God Words often.
หลังจากที่คุณเป็นนักรบ คุณต้องจัดการกับศาสนาของพระวจนะของพระเจ้าบ่อยๆ
It seems the current Warrior doesn't like The Religion of God Words.
ดูเหมือนว่า Warrior คนปัจจุบันจะไม่ชอบ The Religion of God Words
No. There's no such thing.
ไม่ไม่มีสิ่งนั้น
It's okay. That's good.
ไม่เป็นไร. ดีแล้ว.
The pontiff of The Religion of God Words, Dustin,
สังฆราชแห่งพระวจนะแห่งศาสนา ดัสติน
may look like a friendly old man, but never open yourself to him.
อาจดูเหมือนชายชราที่เป็นมิตร แต่อย่าเปิดใจกับเขา
Lest you will be like your brother, being abandoned after he makes use of your soul.
เกรงว่าเจ้าจะเป็นเหมือนพี่น้องของเจ้า ถูกทอดทิ้งหลังจากเขาใช้จิตวิญญาณของเจ้า
What does that mean?
นั่นหมายความว่าอย่างไร?
Half-elf?
สิบโมงครึ่ง?
It's been awhile since Schlain was chosen as Warrior and brought back to the castle.
นานแล้วที่ Schlain ได้รับเลือกให้เป็นนักรบและถูกนำตัวกลับไปที่ปราสาท
How is he now?
ตอนนี้เขาเป็นอย่างไรบ้าง
The door isn't locked.
ประตูไม่ได้ล็อค
Katia...
คาเทีย...
Sue, are you alright?
ซู คุณสบายดีไหม
I'm very sad about Brother Julius' death. I'm of course worried about Brother Schlain too.
ฉันเสียใจมากเกี่ยวกับการตายของบราเดอร์จูเลียส ฉันก็เป็นห่วงพี่ชเลนเหมือนกัน
But I'm fine.
แต่ฉันสบายดี
Because he's my brother.
เพราะเขาเป็นพี่ชายของฉัน
Yes. You're right.
ใช่. คุณถูก.
Hi, you two.
สวัสดีคุณทั้งสอง
Hugo, didn't you leave the school?
ฮิวโก้ คุณไม่ออกจากโรงเรียนเหรอ
I need your help.
ฉันต้องการความช่วยเหลือจากคุณ.
Help?
ช่วยด้วย?
Yes. However...
ใช่. อย่างไรก็ตาม...
It's a request you can't reject.
เป็นคำขอที่คุณปฏิเสธไม่ได้
Please wait where you are.
กรุณารอที่ที่คุณอยู่
Okay.
ตกลง.
What happened?
เกิดอะไรขึ้น?
SO I'M A SPIDER, SO WHAT?
ฉันเป็นแมงมุม แล้วไง
I'm so happy to have a walk.
ฉันมีความสุขมากที่ได้เดินเล่น
Although I only left home for school in my past life,
ถึงแม้ว่าฉันจะออกจากบ้านเพื่อไปโรงเรียนในชาติที่แล้ว
I'm now a good and healthy baby who has walks.
ตอนนี้ฉันเป็นเด็กที่ดีและมีสุขภาพดีที่เดินได้
INVESTIGATION
ตรวจสอบ
Mother's subordinates.
ลูกน้องของแม่.
They look very angry.
พวกเขาดูโกรธมาก
"ARCH TARATECT LEVEL 31" Let's see. Seriously?
"ARCH TARATECT ระดับ 31" มาดูกัน อย่างจริงจัง?
Its ability value is as good as Araba's.
ค่าความสามารถของมันดีเท่ากับของอราบา
The leader is an Arch Taratect.
ผู้นำคืออาร์คทาราเทค
There are three Greater Taratects. They're strong as well.
มีสามมหานคร Taratects พวกมันแข็งแกร่งเช่นกัน
And some other spiders.
และแมงมุมอื่นๆ
I can only... fight!
ฉันทำได้แค่... สู้!
I've been waiting for you, brothers and sisters.
ฉันรอคุณอยู่นะ พี่น้อง
This is your cemetery.
นี่คือสุสานของคุณ
Bring it on and fall into the trap.
นำมันและตกลงไปในกับดัก
They found it out immediately.
พวกเขาค้นพบทันที
There isn't just one trap.
ไม่ได้มีเพียงหนึ่งกับดัก
Come on. Have a taste of my Diablo Bullets.
มาเลย ลิ้มรส Diablo Bullets ของฉัน
I've revenged!
ฉันแก้แค้นแล้ว!
It's indeed hard to defeat taratects which are as good as dragons.
เป็นการยากที่จะปราบทาราเทกที่เก่งพอๆ กับมังกร
Oh no! It's spider silks!
ไม่นะ! มันคือใยแมงมุม!
It can actually turn automatically.
มันสามารถหมุนอัตโนมัติได้จริง
"LEVEL 10 SILK CONTROL" They're my siblings indeed.
“การควบคุมไหมระดับ 10” พวกเขาเป็นพี่น้องกันจริงๆ
It's no wonder they have the same skills.
ไม่น่าแปลกใจที่พวกเขามีทักษะเหมือนกัน
The main weapon of the Arch Taratect is level 10 deadly venom attack, silk control
อาวุธหลักของอาร์คทาราเทคคือพิษร้ายแรงระดับ 10 ควบคุมไหม
and Utility Silk.
และยูทิลิตี้ไหม
Its ability value is as high as a dragon's and it has powerful companions.
ค่าความสามารถของมันสูงเท่ากับมังกรและมีสหายที่ทรงพลัง
I can't win if they attack together.
ฉันไม่สามารถชนะได้หากพวกเขาโจมตีด้วยกัน
So I won't attack you all at the same time.
ดังนั้นฉันจะไม่โจมตีคุณทั้งหมดในเวลาเดียวกัน
Okay. Almost there.
ตกลง. เกือบจะมี.
Oh no!
ไม่นะ!
I almost got killed.
ฉันเกือบถูกฆ่าตาย
I will not be killed by you.
ฉันจะไม่ถูกฆ่าโดยคุณ
There it is.
นั่นเองค่ะ
With such a huge body size, you won't be able to escape the mesh.
ด้วยขนาดตัวที่ใหญ่โตเช่นนี้ คุณจะไม่สามารถหลบหนีจากตาข่ายได้
Although we can use the same skills,
แม้ว่าเราจะใช้ทักษะเดียวกันได้
you think you can defeat me, who has human brain?
คุณคิดว่าคุณสามารถเอาชนะฉันได้ ใครมีสมองของมนุษย์?
Not happy? But the show just about to begin.
ไม่ได้มีความสุข? แต่การแสดงเพิ่งจะเริ่ม
Take this!
เอานี่!
Killing strike!
ลอบสังหาร!
Spatial magic, Teleport!
เวทมนตร์เชิงพื้นที่ เทเลพอร์ต!
How does it feel? Hot?
รู้สึกอย่างไร? ร้อน?
Very hot, right? I feel it too.
ร้อนมากใช่มั้ย? ฉันรู้สึกเช่นกัน
The attraction of Middle Stratum, Great Elroe Labyrinth. Enjoy the lava.
เสน่ห์ของชั้นกลาง Great Elroe Labyrinth เพลิดเพลินไปกับลาวา
Drop into the hot lava.
หยดลงในลาวาร้อน
It's Spatial Maneuver.
เป็นการซ้อมรบเชิงพื้นที่
I will die even if I don't let. I shall just finish this first.
ฉันจะตายแม้ว่าฉันจะไม่ปล่อยให้ ฉันขอจบแค่นี้ก่อน
Take this!
เอานี่!
Take this! Break and fall!
เอานี่! แตกแล้วตก!
Die!
เดอะ!
Healing Magic?
เวทมนตร์บำบัด?
It actually has such a skill.
มันมีทักษะดังกล่าวจริงๆ
Besides, the floor seems to have increased. It could hold longer.
นอกจากนี้พื้นดูเหมือนจะเพิ่มขึ้น มันสามารถอยู่ได้นานขึ้น
Its resistance against Diablo Bullets has increased as well.
การต้านทานต่อ Diablo Bullets ก็เพิ่มขึ้นเช่นกัน
Oh no!
ไม่นะ!
If I don't deal with this fast, it will get even worse.
ถ้าฉันไม่จัดการกับเรื่องนี้อย่างรวดเร็ว มันจะยิ่งแย่ลงไปอีก
How could there be such a stupid thing?
มันจะมีเรื่องโง่ๆ แบบนั้นได้ยังไง?
The situation was favourable for me yet I couldn't kill it.
สถานการณ์เอื้ออำนวยสำหรับฉัน แต่ฉันก็ไม่สามารถฆ่ามันได้
Die!
เดอะ!
Don't waste food.
ไม่ต้องเสียอาหาร
That was close. It almost turned defeat into victory.
มันปิด. มันเกือบจะเปลี่ยนความพ่ายแพ้เป็นชัยชนะ
Experience achieved a certain target.
ประสบการณ์บรรลุเป้าหมายบางอย่าง
I had a two-level upgrade.
ฉันมีการอัพเกรดสองระดับ
Although being dangerous, you're very delicious.
แม้จะอันตรายแต่คุณก็อร่อยมาก
Let's have dessert after the delicious main course.
มาทานของหวานกันหลังจานหลักแสนอร่อยกันเถอะ
You're shivering out of fear.
คุณตัวสั่นด้วยความกลัว
If your superior saw this, it would have retreated as well.
ถ้าหัวหน้าของคุณเห็นสิ่งนี้ มันก็คงจะถอยเช่นกัน
Teleport.
เทเลพอร์ต
Watch this.
ดูนี้.
Don't waste food.
ไม่ต้องเสียอาหาร
I'm finally outside
ในที่สุดฉันก็อยู่ข้างนอก
yet I'm eating the same food as inside.
แต่ฉันกินอาหารแบบเดียวกับข้างใน
Another angry message from mother.
อีกข้อความโกรธจากแม่
She's really mad.
เธอบ้าจริงๆ
I don't want to obey her order at all and this is annoying.
ฉันไม่อยากเชื่อฟังคำสั่งของเธอเลย มันน่ารำคาญ
Can't I just unplug it like a phone?
ฉันไม่สามารถถอดปลั๊กเหมือนโทรศัพท์ได้หรือไม่?
That means there's a channel between mother and I.
นั่นหมายความว่ามีช่องทางระหว่างแม่กับฉัน
It's time.
ได้เวลา.
What's the matter?
เกิดอะไรขึ้น?
I have to say goodbye to you temporarily.
ฉันต้องบอกลาคุณชั่วคราว
What are you talking about?
คุณกำลังพูดถึงอะไร
What does this mean?
สิ่งนี้หมายความว่า?
I want to fight back.
ฉันต้องการที่จะต่อสู้กลับ
What?
อะไร?
Fight back?
สู้กลับ?
Please go to mother.
กรุณาไปหาแม่
What do you mean?
คุณหมายถึงอะไร
I want the three of you
ฉันต้องการคุณสามคน
to launch an attack on mother along this channel that connects to her.
เพื่อเริ่มโจมตีแม่ตามช่องทางนี้ที่เชื่อมต่อกับเธอ
That sounds sinister.
นั่นฟังดูน่ากลัว
After all, it's connected to mother's spirit.
ท้ายที่สุดมันเชื่อมโยงกับจิตวิญญาณของแม่
Me!
ผม!
Speak up, the person of magic number one.
พูดขึ้น บุคคลแห่งเวทมนตร์หมายเลขหนึ่ง
What specifically do you mean by attack?
คุณหมายถึงอะไรโดยเฉพาะโดยการโจมตี?
I don't know.
ฉันไม่รู้
What?
อะไร?
You don't know either?
คุณไม่รู้เหมือนกันหรือ
Don't worry. We can do it as long as we work hard for it.
ไม่ต้องกังวล เราสามารถทำได้ตราบใดที่เราทำงานหนักเพื่อมัน
It's better than doing nothing.
ดีกว่าไม่ทำอะไรเลย
Never try, never know.
ไม่เคยลองไม่เคยรู้
That's right.
ถูกตัอง.
That's all, everyone.
เท่านั้นแหละทุกคน
Thank you so much.
ขอบคุณมาก.
Roger.
โรเจอร์.
Nosukezaemon.
โนสุเกะซาเอมอน.
Here it is. Engulf her spirit.
นี่มัน. ดูดกลืนจิตวิญญาณของเธอ
Yes.
ใช่.
Thank you, everyone.
ขอบคุณทุกคน.
♫This is annoying. I'm sure I won♫
♫นี่มันน่ารำคาญ ฉันแน่ใจว่าฉันชนะ♫
♫Weak one (swallow it) Strong ones (Exhausted). Take it as nutrition♫
♫ตัวอ่อน (กลืนเข้าไป) ตัวที่แข็งแรง (หมดแรง) ใช้เป็นสารอาหาร ♫
♫"Again! Again!" What a boring game♫
♫"อีกครั้ง!อีกครั้ง!" ช่างเป็นเกมที่น่าเบื่อ♫
♫Don't look down at life♫
♫อย่าดูถูกชีวิต♫
♫Fooled. I knew your intelligence is wrong♫
♫โง่เขลา ฉันรู้ว่าสติปัญญาของคุณผิด♫
♫Tell me how it feels to be fooled by an inferior animal♫
♫บอกฉันทีว่ารู้สึกอย่างไรที่ถูกสัตว์ที่ด้อยกว่าหลอกมา♫
♫I'm still happy over your misery today. I shall start eating now♫
♫ฉันยังคงมีความสุขกับความทุกข์ยากของคุณในวันนี้ ฉันจะเริ่มกินแล้ว ♫
♫Unreasonable, unlucky, so what?♫
♫ไร้เหตุผล โชคร้าย แล้วไงล่ะ♫
♫I want to try my best to live♫
♫ฉันอยากจะพยายามใช้ชีวิตให้ดีที่สุด♫
♫Succeeded. I almost got all of you♫
♫ประสบความสำเร็จ เกือบได้ทุกคนแล้ว ♫
♫Silk control. Venomous fangs. Sure-win strategy. Watch it♫
♫ควบคุมไหม เขี้ยวพิษ. กลยุทธ์ที่ชนะแน่นอน ดูมัน♫
♫Victory! No one can stop me♫
♫ชัยชนะ! ไม่มีใครหยุดฉันได้ ♫
♫Despite the failed reincarnation, I want to keep living♫
♫ถึงแม้ว่าการเกิดใหม่จะล้มเหลว ฉันก็ยังอยากมีชีวิตอยู่ต่อไป♫
♫Defeat! Great! Spider! Good!♫
♫พ่ายแพ้! เยี่ยมมาก! แมงมุม! ดี!♫
♫Defeat! No problem! Spider's style! (Die, die die)♫
♫พ่ายแพ้! ไม่มีปัญหา! สไตล์แมงมุม! (ตาย ตาย ตาย) ♫
I reached the destination safely.
ฉันถึงที่หมายอย่างปลอดภัย
That's great.
ที่ที่ดี
Wait and see, Schlain.
รอดูต่อไป ชเลน
SO I'M A SPIDER, SO WHAT? NEXT EPISODE: YOU REBELLIOUS, I SELF-ABUSIVE
ฉันเป็นแมงมุม แล้วไง ตอนต่อไป: คุณเป็นคนทรยศ ฉันทำร้ายตัวเอง
STAY TUNED
คอยติดตาม